I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you, I am always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame
We were all swept away
I'll come and get you; I am always ready to fight
Don't take all of the weight
You always do
There will always be something you cannot control
So don't take all of the blame
We will overcome. Your salvation has begun
We were all swept away
Don't take all of the weight
You always do
No signs, no lights
There will always be something you cannot control
Such a mess all over
We will overcome
Don't kill your hopes
Your salvation has begun
You make me realize who I need
No signs, no lights
Such a mess all over
I'll be there, hold on
Don't kill your hopes
They'll change you somehow
You make me realize who I need
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
I'll be there, hold on
The shadows appear
They'll change you somehow
Illusions are born
So where are you now?
The fallen angels you run with don't know
I'll reach you by dawn
The shadows appear
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
Illusions are born
Torn old sepia photographs show
The fallen angels you run with don't know
Our fragile preious world
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
Must discard it, respond to the call
Torn old sepia photographs show
本字幕由诸神字幕组出品，仅供学习交流，禁止用于商业用途
更多中日双语字幕，尽在 i.kamigami.org 和微博 @诸神字幕组
日听:鱼子酱&paper   翻译:小悠&冰蝶   校对:夜神&Lucifer   时间轴:阿水   压制:久嘉
Our fragile precious world
Must discard it, respond to the call
Dawn of
Extermination
This is it.
ここです
Honestly, you may be able to manage,
since you have the Black Demon Series.
正直　黒鬼シリーズを使えるあなた方は
なんとかなる可能性もありますが…
But if we're doing this, I want us to crush them and come out without even a scratch.
どうせやるなら　無傷で敵を皆殺しにしたい
So don't act on impulse—
なので　独断専行は…
I won't.
しねぇよ　無傷でやつらを皆殺し　いいじゃねぇか
Crush them without even a scratch, huh?
I like that.
では行きましょうか
Then let's move.
情報によると　吸血鬼は7人
Based on that girl's information,
the vampires outnumber us seven to five.
我々よりも多いです
Chances are they're sleeping,
so we're going to charge in at full force.
なので　吸血鬼が眠りについている可能性の高いこの時間に
奇襲攻撃を行います
Keep formation, watch each other's backs,
陣形を崩さず　お互いを守り　絶対はぐれないように
and stay together.
これは…
This is...
The clothes of livestock.
家畜の服…
行くぞ
Let's go.
We're heading straight to floor B3,
where the vampires supposedly are.
吸血鬼がいるという　B3フロアまで一気に進む
Why don't they escape
while the vampires' backs are turned?
吸血鬼はいないのに　あいつらはなんで逃げない
Because it's crawling with monsters outside.
外はバケモノだらけだからなぁ
あの人たちは吸血鬼の庇護を受けているのです
They're getting protection from the vampires.
In return for their blood?
血を与える代わりにか
That's why we're going to rescue them.
だからあたしたちで解放するんだ
Everyone, prepare to attack!
総員攻撃準備
Draw!
抜刀
Before they call for backup—
仲間を呼ばれる前に
You cursed swine...
この…家畜が
How does it feel to be killed by livestock, scum?
その家畜に殺される気分はどうだ　吸血鬼
Burn in Hell.
消えろ
この馬鹿が
Seriously?
あれほど独断専行はするなと言ったはずだぞ
How many times have I told you
not to act on your own?!
I didn't act on my own.
独断専行じゃねぇ
敵は非武装だった
The enemy was unarmed,
and I waited for the command to draw.
抜刀の命令も待った
お前こそ　戦場でグダグダ言ってんじゃ…
You need to quit complaining on the battle—
いいね　こういうのを待ってたんだよ
Hell yeah.
I've waited four years for moments like these!
4年もな
Fool.
馬鹿め　そんな大振りで我を殺す…
A wild swing like that won't even graze me—
Wh-What's with that power?
な…なんだあの力は
Oh my!
グレン中佐の秘蔵っ子ですから
I knew he was strong,
being Lieutenant Colonel Guren's favorite and all,
強いってのは分かってましたが　まさかこれほどまでとは
but I didn't think he'd be this strong.
That was awesome, Yuu!
すごいよ　優くん
Still not as strong as me, though.
俺よりは弱えけどな
What?
Let's see you try and do better, then.
じゃあてめぇの実力見せてみろよ
You picking a fight?
んだとこらぁ
Do you know what'll happen if I go all out?
本気出したらどうなるか分かってんのかおい
Bring it!
やってみろや
Damn straight I'll bring it.
やってやろうじゃねぇか
Now, now...
まあまあ
Those two...
The hell? I'll kick your ass.
こいつら…
構えろこらぁ
They're the Lieutenant Colonel's boys—
グレン中佐のお気に入りのチームワークのない問題児たちです
troublemakers who struggle with teamwork.
だからみっちゃんに育ててもらおうと思ったんじゃないですかねぇ
Perhaps that's why he thought you could train them.
Stop mucking around.
お前ら浮かれるな
敵はまだ5人残ってるんだぞ
There are still five of them left.
Here they come.
お出ましか
Let's do this.
やるぞ
Mitsuba!
三葉
Eight of them?!
8人？
Wh-What's going on?
ど…どういうことだ
This isn't what we were told—
情報と数が…
Told?
情報　それは誰が出した情報かな
Told by whom, exactly?
I want to show my appreciation.
助けてもらった　お礼を…
You used a child to...
貴様ら…子供を利用して…
人間は醜いよなぁ
Humans are vile.
家族や仲間を人質にされたら
They'll easily betray their own kind
if it means saving a friend or family member.
平気で同族を売る
Stop!
止せ
Forget about me!
あたしはもう終わりだ　逃げろ
Run!
何度も同じこと言わせんじゃねぇ
Don't make me repeat myself!
I'm not going to leave a comrade behind!
仲間を見捨てて逃げるわけねぇだろうが
I'll get you out of there right now!
今すぐ　お前を助ける
Go!
行け
S-Stop...
やめろ…
Fall back!
Please, stop...
やめ…てくれ
Pathetic livestock.
家畜が
He did it!
やった
お前ら　さっきなんつった
What was it that you said, again?
人間は醜い
"Humans are vile"?
"Scum that betray their own kind if it means saving a friend or family member?"
家族を人質に取られたら
平気で同族を売るクズだって
そりゃあよくご存知で
Looks like someone's done their research.
That's exactly right.
そうだよ　家族のためなら　人間は何でもする
Humans will do anything for their family.
Even if it means shamelessly lying
平気で嘘をつくし
or turning into a devil or demon.
鬼にでも悪魔にでもなる
If that's vile,
それを醜いってんなら
then fear our depraved acts, and keel over, vampires!
その人間の醜さに怯えながら死ね　ヴァンパイア
Christ, he's so damn annoying.
ったく　めんどくせー奴が仲間だなぁ
Oh well. Let's do this thing. With all of us here...
じゃあやるか　このメンバーなら
...it'll be a piece of cake.
やれるでしょう
どうやら二級武装の吸血鬼しかいないようですし
It seems like they're all armed with Class 2 weapons.
Th-They still outnumber us, though.
て…敵の数の方が多いよ
We went in expecting no less.
当初の予定通りだろ
So what now?
どうする
It's time.
行くぞ　吸血鬼を殲滅する
We'll exterminate the vampires!
I see...
そう　よかった
Thank goodness.
Um...
あの
I-I'm so sorry!
ご…ごめんなさい
わ…私…私
I...
お前は自分の仲間を守ろうとした　それだけだ
You were trying to protect your friends.
That's all.
B-But...
で…でも
You did the right thing,
お前は正しいことをしたんだ
だから謝るな
so don't apologize.
Rescued from her perch atop the tower,
窮地から救い出してくれた彼
そんな彼に熱い視線を送る彼女
the once damsel in distress
gazes at him passionately.
Destined, the two slowly fall...
やがて二人は　宿命的な恋に
Not in love!
落ちるか　馬鹿が
Idiot.
What's his deal?
何なんだ　あいつは
Why does he...
あいつはなんで
優さんは子供の頃
Yuu was held captive
at the vampires' city when he was a kid.
吸血鬼の都市に収容されていたんですよ
But one day...
でもある日
Is it true, what Shinoa said?
シノアの話は本当か
お前は　吸血鬼の都市に仲間を置いて
That you left your family behind at the vampires' city...
That's none of your business.
勝手に聞いてんじゃねぇよ
Keep out of my past.
俺の過去に立ち入るな
Wait!
待て
You...
お前は…
I probably don't have any right to say something like this,
あたしにこんなこと言う資格なんてないけど
but I don't think you were in the wrong.
でも　お前は間違っていない　と思う
Maybe not.
かもな　でも俺は
But I left my family behind
in order to save my own life.
自分が逃げるために　仲間を見捨てた
That fact still remains.
その事実は変わらない
That's why I'll never...
だから　もう二度と…
Tsk. Forget it.
もういいだろ
Yuu!
優
What now? Do you still...
なんだよ　まだなんか
そ　その
U-Um, so... earlier...
先は　あ…あり
Th-Tha—
Are you going to tell me or what?
なんだよ
Whatever!
とにかく　私はお前が嫌いだ
I still hate you!
またそれかよ
What did I do?!
How long are you two gonna mess around?
Let's get going already.
おい　お前ら　いつまでじゃれてんだ　行くぞ
Sh-Shut up!
だ　黙れ
No way!
お前マジでできんの
You seriously know how to do that?
おあ
Yeah.
マジのマジ　すっげぇな　お前
Like, for real? Seriously?
That's freakin' awesome, dude!
Shut up already.
うるさいぞ
いやでも俺　子供の時しか車乗ったことねぇからさぁ
You know, I haven't ridden in a car since I was little.
吸血鬼の都市は車なんてなかったし
The vampires' city didn't have any,
渋谷じゃガソリンが貴重だって車なんかほとんど
and gasoline's so precious
that you don't see a lot of it in Shibuya.
Whoa!
マジかよ　すげえ
Holy crap!
This is so cool!
よし
There we go.
ってあれかな　あの　俺もちょっと運転していいのかな
Hey, can I, like... give it a spin?
What? You don't even know how to drive.
お前運転できないだろ
いや　でもさあ　ちょっとだけなら
Yeah, but just for a little while...
とにかく触るな　後でちょっとなら教えてやるから
Don't fiddle with anything.
I'll give you a short lesson later.
お前運転もできんのかよ　マジですげえな
You can drive, too?!
You're way too awesome, man!
い　いいからガキは後部座席に乗ってろ
Wh-Whatever. Just hop in the back, you five-year-old.
意外と美味しいですね
This is surprisingly good.
動いたぞ　これで新宿はすぐだ
It's running.
We'll get to Shinjuku quicker this way.
Wow.
本当に動いたんですか
Is it really running?
車泥棒は犯罪だぞ　君月
Grand theft auto is a crime, Kimizuki.
うるせぇ　早く行くぞ
Oh, who cares? Let's get going.
Oh man, this ain't good.
やっべぇ　やべぇ
じゃ　こうか
How about this?
お前　何やっ
What the hell are you—Whoa!
てめえ　ぶっ殺すぞ
I'm gonna freaking kill you!
乗れよ　俺が新宿連れてってやる
Get in. I'll take you guys to Shinjuku.
うるせぇ　いいからてめぇは降りろ
You're such a pain in the ass! Just get out already!
Hey, what are you doing?!
何すんだ　コラ
Shut up!
うるせぇ
ったく　あいつらは何をやってるんだ
Seriously, what are they doing?
さあて　じゃ　シノア号に乗ってさっさと新宿行きますか
Well, then.
Let's all get in the Shinoamobile and head to Shinjuku, shall we?
シノア号
The Shinoamobile?
皆さん　早く乗ってください
Hop in, kids!
あれ
Eh? Um...
お前の身長じゃ無理だろ
Can you even see past the dashboard?
You're so short, Shinoa!
シノア　背小っちゃ
なるほど
I see.
もう　シノアは身長でからかうのはやめよう
Yeah...
We should probably leave
Shinoa's height alone from now on.
初めて意見が合ったな
For the first time, I agree with you.
なんだ
What's that sound?
また「ヨハネの四騎士」か
A Horseman again?
始末するか
Should we take care of it?
いや　あいつら殺しても際限ないからな
No.
If you start killing them now, you'll be at it for days.
逃げ切れるならこのまま新宿に
If we can lose them, we'll go on ahead to Shinjuku.
待て
Wait.
音がするのは新宿の方だぞ
The sound's coming from Shinjuku.
皆さん　とりあえず臨戦態勢で
Stay on the alert for the time being.
あらゆる状況に対応出来るようにしてください
Be prepared to handle any kind of situation.
次の角を曲がったら　新宿の防御壁が見えるはずだ
We'll see Shinjuku's defensive barrier after I make a turn at the next corner.
これは
What the...
止まるな　君月
Don't stop, Kimizuki!
貴族だ　このまま轢け
Ram him! He's a noble!
What?!
You...
このっ
剣よ
Drink,
私の血を吸いなさい
my sword.
うそっ
No way!
与一
Yoichi!
これは　まずい
This isn't looking too good.
みなさん　独断で動かないで
Stay in your positions!
相手は一級武装の吸血鬼です
The vampire is armed with a Class 1 weapon!
これまでの吸血鬼とは
He isn't like the other vam—
Hm, not bad for a human.
人間のわりにはやるねぇ
何者なのかな
Who might you be?
こいつ
You...
シノア
Shinoa.
ええ
Yes.
一対一でもすぐには殺されない　優さん　君月さんは前衛に
Yuu and Kimizuki will be the vanguards,
since they won't easily fall in a one-on-one.
私　みっちゃん　与一さんで援護しながら　あの吸血鬼を始末
Mitsu, Yoichi, and I will back them up
and take care of that vampire...
Shoot.
くそ
一気に状況が変わった
Things just took a turn for the worse.
どうする　撤退か
What now? Do we retreat?
逃げられるならそうしたいですが
We would if we could,
あのレベルが三人もいては無理でしょう
but I doubt those three would allow it.
だから　戦います
So we'll fight with everything we have,
on the verge of demon possession.
鬼が暴走する　ギリギリの全力で
しかし　それでも恐らくは
However, even with that...
死者が出る
...there's no guarantee we'll all survive. But that's life on the battlefield.
だが　それが戦場だ
分かってて来たんだろう
You came in expecting as much, right?
なるほど　そういう展開か
I see. So that's the way it's gonna be.
だが　絶対誰も殺させねぇぞ
But I'm not gonna let anyone die.
そのために　俺は力を手に入れたんだ
That's why I have this power.
なあ　阿朱羅丸
Right, Asuramaru?
クローリー様
Lord Crowley, what are you doing here?
こんなところで　何やってるんですかあ
前線で第七位始祖様がお呼びです
The Seventh Progenitor
is waiting for you at the front line.
ん　フェリド君が私を
Ferid is waiting for me?
それは行かないとまずいね
Well, I mustn't keep him any longer.
ここもちょっと面白くなってきたんだけどなぁ
Just when things were getting interesting, too.
ま　それは次の機会でいいか
I guess it can wait for another day.
今回は見逃してあげるけど　でも次は君の血を吸わせてもらうからね
I'll let you go this once.
But the next time we meet, your blood will be mine.
What?!
じゃあねぇ　可愛い家畜君たち
See you later, my cute little lambs.
や　やった　助かった
G-Good... We're saved.
あの野郎　ふざっけんな
That guy...
Damn him!
余裕顔で馬鹿にしやがって
Taking us for fools and playing it cool!
騒ぐな　奴らの気が変わる前にすぐ移動するぞ
Stop whining.
We need to move immediately before they change their mind.
新宿部隊と合流する
We'll rendezvous with the Shinjuku Units.
くそ　なんだよこれ
I can't believe this!
鬼呪装備使ってもこんなに力の差があんのかよ
There's still this much difference in power,
even with Infernal Arms?
まあ　黒鬼装備の優さんなら
Well, since you own the Black Demon Series,
鬼呪の使い方を覚えれば　少しくらいは実力差は埋まりますが
you can narrow the gap a little by learning curses.
なら早く教えろよ
Then hurry up and teach me already!
ですが　あなた一人が吸血鬼と互角になったところでどうなりますか
But what good is it if you're the only one
who can fight a vampire on equal ground?
その間に私は殺されます　みっちゃんも　与一さんも
While you're busy fighting, I'll already be dead.
So will Mitsu and Yoichi.
だから　チームワークがいる
That's why we need teamwork.
今回はいい勉強になりました
This was a good lesson.
死者が出なかったという幸運にも恵まれました
We were also fortunate enough to avoid any casualties.
優さんが自分から撤退を提案してくれたのも嬉しかったです
I was happy that you suggested for us to retreat.
何より
But most importantly...
命を助けてくれてありがとう
Thank you for saving my life.
あなたはグレン中佐が言ったとおり　仲間想いですね
Like Lieutenant Colonel Guren said,
you care about your friends.
い　いや　そ　その
Well, um...
I kinda want to go back to Shibuya already.
なんか　もう渋谷に帰りたいなぁ
同感だが　そういうわけにはいかないだろ
Same here, but we really can't.
新宿が落ちたら　次は渋谷だ
If Shinjuku falls, Shibuya's next.
渋谷にはお前の妹もいるしな
Your sister's in Shibuya, too.
なら　行くぞ
So let's go.
新宿を守るんだ
Let's defend Shinjuku.
ああ
Right.
馴染めた白　鳥がご隅　鼓動獲たツボミも
najimeta shiro torikago sumi
I used to like the light, my corner of the cage
kodou eta tsubomi mo
I'm a flower bud made flesh
置き去り声　眩めた　記憶の影
okizarigoe kurameta kioku no kage
Blinding memories cry after me
I need your blood
i need your blood
You really love 唱える
you read love tonaeru
You speak of love to me
足掻くRed Light
agaku red light
The red lights dance
嗅ぎ分けた音　音と
kagiwaketa neon to
The neon lamps
こじ開けたReasonが
kojiaketa reason ga
and the madness of the world
ただ平行に並ぶ
tada heikou ni narabu
share a vanishing point
Come on break it down for me!
Come on, break it down for me
come on, break it down for me
A river will flow
a river will flow
KEYがない「欲しい」でも　利害鳴る鈴
My desires remain unfulfilled
key ga nai hoshii demo
rigai naru suzu
A melody of ups and downs
懺悔さえ乾いた　４拍子が　奏でた意図を辿る
rigai naru suzu
zange sae kawaita yonbyoushi ga
Our song follows the sheet of our will,
kanadeta ito wo tadoru
no longer capable of penance
木漏れ日の　赤が　騒ぐ
kanadeta ito wo tadoru
Crimson beams assault my vision
komorebi no aka ga sawagu
次回　終わりのセラフ
Next time, on Seraph of the End:
Vampire
Onslaught
"Vampire Onslaught."